Guide to the Artists Space Archive MSS.291
Fales Library and Special Collections
- OVERSIZE Series I: Exhibition Files
  - Zaha Hadid: Exhibition Development, June 4, 2003 (Box 123, Folder 27)
  - L.E.FT - Squatville: Gallery Maps, March 4, 2004 (Box 123, Folder 28)
  - Establishing Shot: Catalogue Draft, March 9, 2004 (Box 123, Folder 29)
  - Based on a True Story: Catalogue Draft, September 14, 2004 (Box 126, Folder 24)
  - Flipside: Poster, November 12, 2004 (Box 126, Folder 25)
  - International Geographic: Kelly Poe Posters, September 16, 2005 (Box 127, Folder 6)
  - Empty Space With Exciting Events: Sonic Godiva Poster, November 16, 2005 (Box 126, Folder 26)
  - Lines for the Next Exhibition, Robert Arndt: Footnotes Poster, November 16, 2005 (Folder 5 Right)
  - Local Transit: Poster, May 16, 2006 (Box 123, Folder 30)
- OVERSIZE Series II: Promotional Materials
  - Artists Space Brochure, January 17, 1991 (Box 124, Folder 1)
  - Artists Space Brochure, March 14, 1991 (Box 124, Folder 2)
  - Artists Space Brochure, May 16, 1991 (Box 124, Folder 3)
  - Artists Space Newsletter: Number 1, Volume 1, September - October 1994 (Box 124, Folder 4)
  - Artists Space Newsletter: Number 2, Volume 1, November 1994 - January 1995 (Box 124, Folder 5)
  - Artists Space Newsletter: Number 3, Volume 1, January - April 1995 (Box 124, Folder 6)
  - Artists Space Newsletter: Number 4, Volume 1, April - July 1995 (Box 124, Folder 7)
  - Artists Space Newsletter: Number 1, Volume 2, September - October 1995 (Box 124, Folder 8)
  - Artists Space Newsletter: Number 2, Volume 2, November 1995 - January 1996 (Box 124, Folder 9)
  - Artists Space Newsletter: Number 2, Volume 3 Draft, January - April 1996 (Box 124, Folder 10)
  - Artists Space Newsletter: Number 2, Volume 3 Draft Centerfold, November 22, 1995 (Box 124, Folder 11)
  - Artists Space Newsletter: Number 2, Volume 3, January - April 1996 (Box 124, Folder 12)
  - Artists Space Newsletter: Number 4, Volume 2 Draft, April - May 1996 (Box 124, Folder 13)
  - Artists Space Newsletter: Number 4, Volume 2, April - May 1996 (Box 124, Folder 14)
  - Artists Space Newsletter: Number 1, Volume 3 Draft, September - October 1996 (Box 124, Folder 15)
  - Artists Space Newsletter: Number 1, Volume 3, September - October 1996 (Box 124, Folder 16)
  - Artists Space Newsletter: Number 2, Volume 3 Draft, November 1996 - January 1997 (Box 124, Folder 17)
  - Artists Space Newsletter: Number 2, Volume 3, November 1996 - January 1997 (Box 124, Folder 18)
  - Artists Space Newsletter: Number 3, Volume 3 Draft, January - March 1997 (Box 124, Folder 19)
  - Artists Space Newsletter: Number 4, Volume 3 Draft, April - May 1997 (Box 124, Folder 20)
  - Artists Space Newsletter: Number 5, Volume 3 Draft, June - July 1997 (Box 124, Folder 21)
  - Artists Space Newsletter: Number 5, Volume 3, June - July 1997 (Box 124, Folder 22)
  - Artists Space Newsletter: Number 1, Volume 4 Drafts, September - October 1997 (Box 124, Folder 23)
  - Artists Space Newsletter: Number 5, Volume 4 Draft, June - July 1998 (Box 126, Folder 27)
  - Artists Space Newsletter: Number 5, Volume 4, June - July 1998 (Box 124, Folder 24)
  - Artists Space Newsletter: Number 5, Volume 5, June - July 1998 (Box 124, Folder 25)
  - Artists Space Newsletter: Number 1, Volume 5, September - November 1998 (Box 124, Folder 26)
  - Artists Space Newsletter: Number 2, Volume 5, November 1998 - January 1999 (Box 124, Folder 27)
  - Artists Space Newsletter: Number 3, Volume 5, February - April 1999 (Box 124, Folder 28)
  - Artists Space Newsletter: Number 1, Volume 6, September - November 1999 (Box 124, Folder 29)
  - Artists Space Newsletter: Number 2, Volume 6, November - December 1999 (Box 124, Folder 30)
  - Artists Space Newsletter: Number 3, Volume 6 Draft, February - March 2000 (Box 125, Folder 1)
  - Artists Space Newsletter: Number 3, Volume 6, February - March 2000 (Box 125, Folder 2)
  - Artists Space Newsletter: Number 4, Volume 6 Draft, April - May 2000 (Box 125, Folder 3)
  - Artists Space Exhibition Brochure Draft, March 8, 2006 (Box 125, Folder 4)
- OVERSIZE Series III: Administrative
  - Subseries A: Gallery Organization
    - Gallery Floorplans, Maps, 1990 - 1992, undated (Folder 14)
    - Demolition Plan, Gallery Plans, Intermediate Scheme, June 19, 1994; undated (Box 126, Folder 28)
    - Employee Calendar, 2000 (Box 126, Folder 29)
    - "Common Room - Jesko Fezer & IJF" Gallery Maps, Photographs, August 25, 2009; undated (Box 125, Folder 5)
    - Lower Manhattan Address Lists, Maps, undated (Box 125, Folder 6)
- OVERSIZE Series IV: Book Files
  - 15th Anniversary Publication: Supporter Lists, November 15, 1988 (Box 125, Folder 7)
  - 15th Anniversary Catalogue: Chronology 1973-1977, June 9, 1989 (Box 125, Folder 8)
  - 15th Anniversary Publication: "Jim Hinchee's Layout", 1989 (Box 125, Folder 9)
  - 15th Anniversary Publication: Chronology 1973 - 1989 Draft, July 26, 1989 (Box 125, Folder 10)
  - "Old Drafts of Chronology": Sit Down & Watch It, Authors in Search of a Publisher - Poster, April 18, 1995 (Box 125, Folder 11)
- OVERSIZE Series V: Independent Project Grants
  - "48 Hours" Harrell Fletcher, Charles Goldman - Poster, April 2002 (Box 125, Folder 12)
- OVERSIZE Series VI: Curator Files
  - Diane Torr: Press Clippings, 1993 - 1994 (Box 125, Folder 13)
  - Marco Papa: Emerging Curators Proposal, 2002 - 2003 (Box 125, Folder 14)
  - "Frieze 2004" [Capri Newspaper, Mark Titchner Poster] (Box 126, Folder 30)
  - Lois & Richard Rosenthal Contemporary Arts Center: Centerbeat Newsletter, Winter 2004 (Box 125, Folder 15)